A Guide to the Papers of Edythe C. Harrison 1961-1993
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
The Papers of Edythe C. Harrison 1961-1993
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
MG 60
Number of containers: 74 document cases, 1 Hollinger box, 1 oversize box-approx. 33 linear ft.
Administrative Information
Access
The collection is open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Edythe C. Harrison, September 1994. A second accession was received in 1998.
Biographical/Historical Information
Edythe C. Harrison was born in Detroit, Michigan in 1934. She has lived in Norfolk, Virginia since 1957. A professional volunteer, Edythe founded and served on numerous committees and councils. She is a founding member of the Virginia Opera Association. She also served on Old Dominion University's President's Advisory Council, the Board of Directors of the Greater Norfolk Corporation, the Advisory Committee of the Day Care and Child Development Center of Tidewater, Inc., and National Board of Governors of the National Conference of Soviet Jewry. In 1980 she was a founding member of Virginians Organized For Informed Community Expression (V.O.I.C.E.), an organization established to counter vocal right-wing attacks on such issues as abortion and medical research on human reproduction and fertility. Additionally in 1983 she chaired the 2nd District chapter of the National Women's Political Caucus. Her awards and honors include Outstanding Professional Woman of the Tidewater, and the Brotherhood Award of the National Conference of Christians and Jews.
Edythe C. Harrison was first elected to political office in 1979 when she was elected to the Virginia House of Delegates. The committees on which she served during her tenure in the House of Delegates, 1979- 1982, were Education, Labor and Commerce, Conservation and Natural Resources, and Chesapeake and its Tributaries. She also served as Chairperson of the Joint Legislative Subcommittee on Vocational-Technical and Career Education and represented Virginia at the National Conference of State Legislatures, Arts and the States Committee. President Jimmy Carter appointed Edythe Harrison to the Advisory Committee for the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts in 1979. In 1982 political redistricting in Norfolk created single member districts. She opposed incumbent Thomas Moss in the Democratic primary and lost. In 1984 Edythe Harrison became the first woman from Virginia nominated to seek state-wide office. She challenged Republican incumbent Senator John Warner in the 1984 United States Senate Race and was defeated.
In 1994 the Harrison Opera House in Norfolk was named for her after she raised $10 million to have the 50-year old civic auditorium completely remodeled and expanded.
Scope and Content Information
The Edythe C. Harrison Collection contains material spanning the years 1961 to 1993, with the bulk of the papers falling between 1979 and 1993. The papers concern her activities in the Virginia House of Delegates from 1979-1982, the Virginia Opera Association, the course she taught at Old Dominion University titled Women in Leadership, and her campaign for United States Senate in 1984 against incumbent Republican Senator John Warner. Also included in the collection are audio and video tapes of Harrison's speeches, radio and TV ads from the 1984 senate campaign, and published reports on the topics of comparable worth and women in politics.
The bulk of the collection pertains to the 1984 United States Senate race, providing considerable insight into how a campaign operates from organizing staff and volunteers, to establishing stances on various issues and soliciting electoral and financial support.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into five series: Legislative Papers, Campaign Files, the Virginia Opera Association, General Papers, Audio and Video Tapes.
Series I: Legislative Papers contains material regarding legislation proposed during Harrison's tenure in the Virginia House of Delegates. Some of the issues covered include; abortion, mastectomy, paternity, arts funding and education.
Sub-series A, contains material regarding legislation proposed during Harrison's tenure in the Virginia House of Delegates.
Sub-series B, involves Harrison's work on the Joint Subcommittee on Career, Technical and Vocational Education that she organized and chaired during her term in the Virginia House of Delegates. This sub- series contains newspaper clippings, correspondence, reports of the committee and House Joint Resolutions.
Series II: Campaign Files contains material regarding the campaign for House of Delegates, the campaign for U.S. Senate and newspaper clippings regarding both campaigns.
Sub-series A, contains information on the elections in 1979, 1981 and her campaign in the 1982 Democratic primary against Delegate Tom Moss of Norfolk.
Sub-series B, contains information on political action committees, fundraising, contributions and contributors, research on various issues, preparatory notes for debates against Warner, reports stating her stance on the issues, political contacts throughout the state and election results in Virginia's ten congressional districts for previous elections. The correspondence includes letters of support, requests for information, letters from her constituents and condolence letters on her defeat. Her records also contain a considerable amount of material on her opponent, Senator John Warner. This material includes information on his Senate voting record, personal life, positions on various issues and contributions to his campaign for United States Senate in 1978.
Sub-series C, contains newspaper clippings regarding Harrison's campaigns. The bulk of this sub-series pertains to the 1984 senate campaign.
Series III: Virginia Opera Association contains reviews of events, news articles, promotional materials, programs from the Virginia Opera and other opera and music festivals. The correspondence contains letters of support to and from the association and nomination letters for the committees of the Virginia Opera Association.
Series IV: General Papers-includes material regarding Harrison's non-legislative activities.
Sub-series A, contains material regarding her work in support of the arts.
Sub-series B, contains information on the Virginia Vocational-Technical Education Foundation (VVEF) later renamed the Virginia Foundation for Business and Education. The material consists of meeting records, correspondence, news clippings, and reports.
Sub-series C, contains material regarding Harrison's work to keep abortion legal. Also included is material on V.O.I.C.E. (Virginians Organized For Informed Community Expression). The folders contain minutes of meetings, stances on abortion, membership solicitations and budget reports. Correspondence contains insightful information on the organization's purpose and the members of the organization. A letter of particular importance is from Pat Robertson to Bob Nusbaum, Vice-President of V.O.I.C.E.
Sub-series D, contains material regarding Harrison's work in women's issues. Most of this material pertains to Harrison's involvement with the National Women's Political Caucus (NWPC).
Sub-series E, contains material regarding the course taught by Harrison at Old Dominion University. The materials include lecture notes, course descriptions, reference materials. The sub series also contains material on the Friends of Women's Studies group at ODU.
Sub-series F, contains miscellaneous materials such as personal correspondence, invitations, certificates, and portrait photos.
Sub-series G, contains published reports mostly concerning the issues of comparable worth and women in politics.
Sub-series H, contains oversized materials, mostly newspapers, also a birthday card, maps of voting precincts, sample ballot, and cross reference directory.
Series V: Audio and Video Tapes contains tapes mostly regarding Harrison's political activities. They include speeches, political ads, appearances on talk and news shows.
Contents List
- Legislative Files
  - House of Delegates 1979-1982
    - Breast Cancer (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mastectomy (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Mastectomy Legislation House Bill 406-Harrison 1982 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Mastectomy Options NCSL Task Force Report 1981 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Legislation Correspondence (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts-appointment, general correspondence (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts-appropriations 1982 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts-appropriation amendment (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Arts Legislation (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts-Constituent Responses HB 1070 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts-Correspondence (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts-Tidewater Grants 1981 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Williams School (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Commission for the Arts-Task Force on the Challenge (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 5)
    - American Arts Alliance (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Arts and the States 1982 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Arts-Legislation (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Alliance for Arts Education-NCSL meeting Nashville (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Education-Arts and Schools (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Arts Education-News Article (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Arts Education (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Arts Education and Brain Research (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Arts Education Association (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Arts Funding I (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Arts Funding II (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Arts Funding-Articles (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Arts Legislation-General Correspondence (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Arts Legislation-Income Tax Deductions (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Arts Legislation-Percentage for the Arts (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Arts Legislation-House Joint Resolution #319, 1981 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Arts Legislation-House Bill #1070, 1981 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Arts Legislation-Tax Deductions for Artists, House Bill #1070 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Arts Legislation-Acquisition of Works of Art, House Bill # 143, Patron-Harrison 1982 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Arts Legislation-Tax Deduction for Artists Bill # 894, Patron-Harrison 1982 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Arts-National Endowment for the Arts (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Arts-News Articles (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Arts-Newsletters (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Arts-Oregon (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Advisory Committee on Arts Education-Meetings (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Friends of Women's Studies (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Congratulatory Letters-1979 Election (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Elections-News Articles General Assembely 1981 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Election-News Clippings (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Election November, 1982 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Election-(General) Sample Ballot November 6, 1979 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Orientation Edythe Harrison General Assembely (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Election Primary 1979 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Lawyer Legislators (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Legislative Ratings-General Assembely 1979 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Norfolk Public Schools-Student Intern Publication (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Norfolk Public Schools-Student Intern Reports (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk Public Schools-General Assembely Internship Program-Lake Taylor High School (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk Public Schools-Q.A. Internship Program 1982 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk Public Schools-Short Term Internship Program (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Election Norfolk Five 1981 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Olympics Resolution (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Paternity Legislation House Bill #355, Patron-Edythe Harrison 1982 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Paternity Test Press Releases June, 1982 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Paternity (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Paternity Test (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Subcommittee on Career, Vocational, Technical Education 1979-1982
    - Study Reports (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Subcommittee Meeting August 3, 1982 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Extended Subcommittee 1982 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Career Education-Polly Liss August 3, 1982 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Career Education Advisory Committee (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Subcommittee Roster 1982 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Edythe Harrison Articles (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Subcommittee's Final Report Press Release and Press Response (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Subcommittee Final Meeting October 5, 1981 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Subcommittee's Final Report 1982 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Subcommittee's Final Report, Correspondence (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 8)
    - News Articles (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Active File (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Legislation:HJR 141 requesting the General Assembly Continue Subcommittee (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Career Coalition Norfolk (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 12)
    - VPI & SU Career Education Conference April 28, 1980 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Career Education Conference 2nd Annual, Blacksburg I July 30, 1981 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Career Education Conference 2nd Annual, Blacksburg II July 30, 1981 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Career Education Definition (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Career Education Handbook for State Policy Makers (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax October 7, 1980 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Vocational Educational Funding of Virginia Community Colleges (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Georgia Senate Committee (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 8)
    - House Joint Resloution #224, Defining Career Education (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 9)
    - House Joint Resloution #225 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 10)
    - House Joint Resloution #97, Correspondence I (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 11)
    - House Joint Resloution #97, Correspondence II (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 12)
    - House Joint Resloution #225, Press Release January 19, 1981 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Interested Persons (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Issues (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Kiwanis Speech June 24, 1981 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 4)
    - House Bill #224, Press Release (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 5)
    - House Joint Resolution #224, Press Release January 19, 1981 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 6)
    - House Bill #225 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 7)
    - House Joint Resolution #97 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 8)
    - House Joint Resolution #20, request General Assembely to adopt recommendations of committee (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Legislation (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 10)
    - House Joint Resolution #97, Legislative Enactment (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Marland's Speech on Career Education (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Meeting in Delegate Philpott's office April 29, 1981 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 13)
    - News/References (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Newsweek Article "Training for the Future" (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Norfolk I, September 23, 1980 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Norfolk II, September 23, 1980 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Norfolk State University Certificate of Appreciation (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Person's Testifying (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Proposal (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Proprietary Schools (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Proposal from Virginia State University Career Development (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 2)
    - House Joint Resolution #97, Research Material I (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 3)
    - House Joint Resolution #97, Research Material II (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 4)
    - House Joint Resolution #97, Research Material III (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Report (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Revisions for the Department of Education (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Richmond September 30, 1980 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Roanoke October 2, 1980 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Roster of Local Administrators for Vocational Education (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Speeches (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Career Education Speech from Conference at Virginia Tech-Thank You Letters (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Speech at the 2nd Career Education Conference, Blacksburg June 29, July 1, 1981 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Speech by Dr. Beamer, Washington D.C. June 20, 1981 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Notes on Speech by Dr. Worthington (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Standards of Quality (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 8)
    - House Joint Resolution #97: Subcommittee Appointments (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Subcommittee Extension 1982 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Subcommittee Meetings I (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Subcommittee Meetings II (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Letter Regarding Work by Committee Members (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Task Force Report Iowa State (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Title 4-A through CETA Career Development (Jim Holley and Pam Kloepel) (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 15)
    - T.R.E.E. (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Council of Local Administrators: Virginia Tech October 16, 1980 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 17)
    - V.P. Youth Employment Report (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Legislation 1980-1981 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Legislation that Edythe Harrison patroned 1982 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 2)
- Campaign Files
  - Campaigns for the House of Delegates 1979-1982
    - News Articles Moss-Harrison Caucus I 1983 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 3)
    - News Articles Moss-Harrison Caucus II 1983 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Campaign 1982 House of Delegates Letters to the Editor (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Newspaper Questionnaire-1979 Election (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Campaign 1979 and 1981 House of Delegates General Election (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Election 1979-Endorsements (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1982 Campaign-Articles (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Campaign 1982-Press Releases (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Campaign 1982-Campaign Flyers & Bumper Stickers (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Campaign 1982-Mandamus Society (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Campaign 1982-PACE Questionnaire (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Tim Horan (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Campaign 1982-News Articles I (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Campaign 1982-News Articles II (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Campaign 1982-Letter sent to Community Leaders picked by Bob Nusbaum (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Campaign 1982-Virginia Pilot Editorials (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Campaign for the United States Senate 1984
    - American Civil Liberties Union 1984 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 7)
    - ADA Voting Record (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 8)
    - American Political Almanac-Virginia Information 1984 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Morris Amitay AIPAC (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'Rith (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Artwork (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Biographies (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Edie Biography (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Biographies-Jewish (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Biography: Political Background (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 16)
    - NAB Broadcasting Agreements (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Brochure-Original (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Budget 1984-Senate Race (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Bulk Mail (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Bumper Stickers 1984 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 21)
    - 1980 Campaign House of Delegates (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Campaign Catalogs (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Catering-Virginia Beach (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Harrison's Civil Rights Records (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Center Theater Rental for Rally-November 1 (Virginia Opera Association) (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence To (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence From (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Debates (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Televsion Debate October 12, 1984 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 4)
    - LOWV Debate [Debate, notes, and correspondence] (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Capital Correspondence Debate (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Delegates 1981 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Democratic Convention 1984 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party Press Event July 28, 1984 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Democratic State Central Committee-Virginia (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Democratic Party Plan (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Federation of Democratic Women's Clubs (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Young Democrats (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Democratic Party "How-To" Book (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Democratic National Committee 1984 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Democratic National Committee: Women's Vote Task Forces (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Democratic Newsletters (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Campaign Committee (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Democratic National Training Academy 1984 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Demographics (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Direct Mail (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Endorsements (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Federal Election Commission Regulations (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Congresswoman Geraldine Ferraro-Statement to Virginians July 1984 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Finance Committee (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Joe Fischer (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Flyer-Agriculture (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Flyer-Shipyards (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Reverend John Foster (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Marianne Fowler-Research Project (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Matt Reese & Associates Fundraising Record Form (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 15)
    - John Glenn Campaign (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Governor Charles S. Robb (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 17)
    - House of Representatives Directory 98th Congress 1983-1984 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Ideas: Copies of Candidates Letters I (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Ideas: Copies of Candidates Letters II (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Examples of Campaign Brochures (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Issues, Resources, and Contacts (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Issue Statements-Edie 1984 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Justice Department: Letter to Mr. Gabel re: Virginia Democratic Senate Nomination (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Kiplinger Reports (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Labels (mailing)- Virginia Democrats, Delegates, Senators, State Central, City and Co-Chairs (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 1)
    - League of Women Voters (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 2)